{"data":[{"question":"She gave me to understand she would leaving any day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"gave","b":"understand","c":"leaving","d":"any","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Leaving-> leave","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"His shop has gone into business after making heavy losses.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has gone","b":"into","c":"making","d":"losses","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Into-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"She was one of five astronauts on the space shuttle Challenger, that completed a successful six-day voyage in space in June 1983.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"astronauts","b":"on","c":"that","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- That-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Your friends are taken in his fantastic story of having get to the Pole alone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"fantastic","c":"get","d":"alone","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Got-> gotten","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The successful of our local theatre has put our city on the map.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"successful","b":"local","c":"has put","d":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Successful-> success","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The more I read about history, the more it brings to home to me how relevant history is for us today.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"more","b":"about","c":"to","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nbrings to home -> brings home","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"If you see ever a tall and skinny Chinese boy with a mole on his chin, it's me.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ever","b":"skinny","c":"mole","d":"me","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Ever-> ever see","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"My name is Fang Yaorong and I would be 12 on the first of June this year.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would","b":"be","c":"on","d":"of","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Would-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I wear thickness glasses because I didn't take proper care of my eyesight when I was young.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"thickness","b":"proper","c":"eyesight","d":"when","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Thickness-> thick","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I attend for school in the morning at Ghim Moth Primary School.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for","b":"in","c":"at","d":"Primary","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}